

#### ALEXANDER KUSTOV

Developer & Designer

Russian born, European raised developer who during the last 4 years accomplished to build more than 8 products for various stage startups, relative to European, USA and Japanese markets by doing Full Stack Development and Design services.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Co-Founder & CTO Inspiring Code (Lisbon, PT) 2013 - 2014

Head of IT JADE Europe (Brussels, Belgium) 2012 - 2013

IT Director ISCTE Junior Consulting (Lisbon, PT) 2010 - 2012

### EDUCATION

MOOCs and Independent Courses 2010 - Current

Professor for Web Development University of Central Greece - Greece 2013

Bach. Computer Sciences ISCTE-IUL - Portugal 2008 - 2011

### [抗] SKILLS

HTML/CSS/JS

Ruby on Rails Swift Git MySQL/Postgres/mongoDB Cordova Frameworks Java PHP Lean Startup Development

# **RECENT PROJECTS**

Futuredeck.io - Ruby on Rails LivrosDeOntem.pt - Wordpress SocialVentureCrowd.com - Ruby on Rails

### **LANGUAGES**

CONTACT

Native: English, Portuguese, Russian, Medium: Spanish, French Basic: Japanese

## ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

hello@alexanderkustov.com +44 7904 930585 (UK) +351 919 411 939 (PT)



Futurology, Teaching, Cycling, Guitar Shredding, Startup Mentoring

